<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><title>Dustin Raimondi</title><link href="dustin.raimondi.rocks/" rel="alternate"></link><link href="dustin.raimondi.rocks/feeds/motorcyclestechnology.atom.xml" rel="self"></link><id>dustin.raimondi.rocks/</id><updated>2016-03-06T05:43:18-05:00</updated><entry><title>Motovlogging Technology is awesome</title><link href="dustin.raimondi.rocks/motovlogging-technology-is-awesome.html" rel="alternate"></link><updated>2016-03-06T05:43:18-05:00</updated><author><name>Dustin</name></author><id>tag:,2016-03-06:dustin.raimondi.rocks/motovlogging-technology-is-awesome.html</id><summary type="html">&lt;p&gt;Being equal parts motorcyclist and technology geek, I love it when my two main hobbies cross paths. I'm preparing for an upcoming trip with some friends which I want to record. The amount of technology that facilitates this is wonderful.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h5&gt;GoPro Hero 3+&lt;/h5&gt;
&lt;p&gt;GoPro has been the defacto standard for action cameras for a while now. Back when I had a normal motorcycle helmet, I was not really a fan of the form factor of the Hero cameras, preferring the cartridge style of the Drift and Contour cameras as a helmet mounted optic. These were also waterproof without a case which was awesome. Now that I have a dual sport style helmet with a sun visor to stick a GoPro under, it's not any worse. Also, GoPro really has the peripheral compatibility market cornered, which brings me to my next two items.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h5&gt;Sena 20S&lt;/h5&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Sena's primary line of products are Bluetooth intercoms for motorcyle helmets. You connect the module to the side of your helmet and wire in some speakers and a mic on the inside and suddenly you have a piece of futuristic SpecOps Mercenary armor. I had the last generation Sena, the SMH-10, which was nice but the speakers were lackluster and you were limited to either phone audio or intercom. The new 20S has a phone app to control it and an FM radio receiver. Most importantly though, it has higher quality speakers, and allows you to connect to multiple audio channels at once, meaning you can be listening to music and GPS from your phone channel, while talking to your friends in the intercom channel. It's fantastic.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h5&gt;Sena GoPro Pack&lt;/h5&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Tying the two awesome products above together is a technological wet dream. You can record video from your camera using the GoPro while using your Sena intercom as a microphone. Because the pack connects to your intercom channel, it records all radio chatter, meaning your friend's witty banter after you loop a wheelie gets saved in sync with the footage of your dumb ass hitting the pavement.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h5&gt;Extras&lt;/h5&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Throw in a couple 20,000mah external batteries and 64gb Class 10 U3 SD Cards and suddenly all of your friends can record a while day's ride from each persons perspective, with each person's voice attached. Cut out 10 minutes of highlights at the and of the day and ship it off to your server over night on your Verizon Unlimited 4G plan and you have Motovlogging Nirvana. Coming to an adventure near you soon.&lt;/p&gt;</summary><category term="motorcycles"></category><category term="technology"></category><category term="gopro"></category><category term="sena"></category><category term="transam"></category></entry></feed>